<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LordObscured</title>
    <description>Let&apos;s be fucking dark, shall we?</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 05:41:02 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 05:41:02 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Thoughts on depression pt.1</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Depressed&lt;/em&gt; people (a party I joined long ago), are deeply convinced that nothing good can possibly really happen in their lives.
Or better: anything that &lt;strong&gt;they want&lt;/strong&gt; to happen. &lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;You and your girlfriend are really having a nice time. Wanna move in together? In the same house?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Oh please! For what? To spoil it? So that we will hate each other? God help me!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Mh, this girl you are talking with appears to be flirting with you. Why don’t you move it up into the bedroom?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What!? Are you crazy? So that we have sex and I can disappoint everybody with my horrible performance and my neediness? I’d kill myself, that is a quicker and less painful way to disgrace.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Well, you got the number of the girl of your dreams. All you have to do is text her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Yea sure, that will go well. How did you just forgot that she will immediately sniff my insecurity? I will ruin everything as usual.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yea, the focus here is on relationships, but you get the point.&lt;br /&gt;
If you are depressed, you are convinced that all the good things are just out of your grasp, for one reason or another. The world has turned its back on you, and you are now part of the miserable bunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This way of thinking will inevitably get you exactly there: to an epic fail. Look, depressed people are just smart cows. All other cows, when crossing that mysterious door, will be butchered. Depressed cows know that, somehow, and stay behind the door to complain, lament and wait for time to save them from their horrible situation.&lt;br /&gt;
They avoid being butchered, so they have some more time to stay afloat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without the strong feeling of every door is a butcher’s entrance, depressed people won’t be depressed. They know the worst is awaiting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The next message you receive: yea, that girl is pissed with you and doesn’t want to talk to you anymore.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The next day of your life: the same old shit, just getting slightly worst as time slowly passes by.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The next choice you take: the wrong one, dictated by your infantile internal bullshit rather than adult rational beliefs.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The next relationship you get in: one of you is going to be deadly unsatisfied and leave the other causing incredible pain.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No wonder depressed people start to develop anger! Anger is the only feeling that makes any sense when it is clear that this game is rigged to make you a loser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are angry because you are playing a game (life) which is engineered sot that you, specifically, lose. &lt;br /&gt;
You are angry because your effort and intentions do not matter, your internal mindfuck will always be one step ahead of you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are angry since the solution to all this is very simple and it is to, well, stop being depressed. To give up. To get into that door and be butchered. To make your girlfriend cry and slit her wrists, to being dumped because your girl has found a real man to give her orgasms, to make wrong fucking choices and be underpaid or unemployed at 35, to live, yet live, yet wake up, yet fucking go through another day, plow through another day of shitty life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s it man, that’s what &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; being depressed is all about.
No wonder depressed people stay so! We don’t like to give up! We are quite tenacious actually, we really grip to this situation. &lt;br /&gt;
Actually, the harder reality rains down on us with its non-sense and biased mechanics, the more we grasp and clamp our teeth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I salute you, all depressed people.
You really suck.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 13:46:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/articles/21/thoughts</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/articles/21/thoughts</guid>
        
        
        <category>post</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Little Golden Dawn</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Everything in my life runs the same old way, the same old way
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
of when you left me&lt;br /&gt;
I can’t really hate it, can’t really change it&lt;br /&gt;
I might as well, just start to like it&lt;br /&gt;
you know I would throw it all way for you, I would throw myself &lt;br /&gt;
I don’t care to move on.&lt;br /&gt;
When the catastrophe is real only the foolish move on,&lt;br /&gt;
the wise mourn. &lt;br /&gt;
My place is in mourning, it feels so right,&lt;br /&gt;
I mourn for the world has lost its star,&lt;br /&gt;
its redeeming star, that would make it all turn and squeal &lt;br /&gt;
you would make the whole world turn and squeal&lt;br /&gt;
because you were all that the world needed&lt;br /&gt;
you said all that the world would shut up to listen to &lt;br /&gt;
I was just waiting for your miracle, baby&lt;br /&gt;
I was just waiting for you to become the dawn &lt;br /&gt;
if you still cry you can come here in my arms, you know &lt;br /&gt;
anytime I will hold my little golden dawn &lt;br /&gt;
anything she is tired or sorry&lt;br /&gt;
or wasted or empty &lt;br /&gt;
anytime she does not need to ask &lt;br /&gt;
anytime I can carry you up&lt;br /&gt;
because you make the world go round &lt;br /&gt;
am I so sick am I, so sick to love you &lt;br /&gt;
don’t worry babe, everything is going to be alright &lt;br /&gt;
I will make it alright &lt;br /&gt;
because you are beautiful and only the cruelest of worlds, only the most treacherous of people will not love you.&lt;br /&gt;
it does not matter, if we have to close in&lt;br /&gt;
shut off the light&lt;br /&gt;
turn off the life &lt;br /&gt;
it does not matter baby we can run from it me and you&lt;br /&gt;
we can run if they don’t love you&lt;br /&gt;
it’s not your fault &lt;br /&gt;
I will be your last bunker romance if needs be.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 13:46:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/articles/21/my-little-golden-dawn</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/articles/21/my-little-golden-dawn</guid>
        
        
        <category>post</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will you ever</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Will you ever come back.. to me?
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This waiting room of a life&lt;br /&gt;
I spill out everywhere, and I can’t - yet - drink&lt;br /&gt;
I know I hurt you badly, make you cry&lt;br /&gt;
and even if now I can’t reach you with my voice&lt;br /&gt;
I can reach you with my mind, for here you still exist,&lt;br /&gt;
even tough outside you don’t.&lt;br /&gt;
You are so beautiful, can I just sit?&lt;br /&gt;
Do you know I got so lost?&lt;br /&gt;
It does not really matter, I still carry a picture in my heart.&lt;br /&gt;
Look at me, I am falling down, in the rain&lt;br /&gt;
Look at me, I still smile, you know I like it when you look at me&lt;br /&gt;
Baby, could you make this life even emptier once you are in it?&lt;br /&gt;
Look, I don’t hate on you, for leaving, haha for hating&lt;br /&gt;
don’t mind really&lt;br /&gt;
don’t mind at all,&lt;br /&gt;
why should a man mind of the tallest mountain, when he already walked its highest peak?&lt;br /&gt;
just hug me baby, even if you don’t care&lt;br /&gt;
life is not much better at all, look, it’s all scattered out for you&lt;br /&gt;
I’m leaving you know, leaving you to this beautiful brunch with your friends&lt;br /&gt;
I have a very long walk awaiting, in which I can think of you&lt;br /&gt;
and I will sing:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;“meet me on the other side,&lt;br /&gt;
where as a rose I will wake …”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 13:04:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/articles/21/will-you-ever</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/articles/21/will-you-ever</guid>
        
        
        <category>post</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
