<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LordObscured</title>
    <description>Let's be fucking dark, shall we?</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 17:11:31 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 17:11:31 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Little Golden Dawn</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Everything in my life runs the same old way, the same old way
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
of when you left me&lt;br /&gt;
I can’t really hate it, can’t really change it&lt;br /&gt;
I might as well, just start to like it&lt;br /&gt;
you know I would throw it all way for you, I would throw myself &lt;br /&gt;
I don’t care to move on.&lt;br /&gt;
When the catastrophe is real only the foolish move on,&lt;br /&gt;
the wise mourn. &lt;br /&gt;
My place is in mourning, it feels so right,&lt;br /&gt;
I mourn for the world has lost its star,&lt;br /&gt;
its redeeming star, that would make it all turn and squeal &lt;br /&gt;
you would make the whole world turn and squeal&lt;br /&gt;
because you were all that the world needed&lt;br /&gt;
you said all that the world would shut up to listen to &lt;br /&gt;
I was just waiting for your miracle, baby&lt;br /&gt;
I was just waiting for you to become the dawn &lt;br /&gt;
if you still cry you can come here in my arms, you know &lt;br /&gt;
anytime I will hold my little golden dawn &lt;br /&gt;
anything she is tired or sorry&lt;br /&gt;
or wasted or empty &lt;br /&gt;
anytime she does not need to ask &lt;br /&gt;
anytime I can carry you up&lt;br /&gt;
because you make the world go round &lt;br /&gt;
am I so sick am I, so sick to love you &lt;br /&gt;
don’t worry babe, everything is going to be alright &lt;br /&gt;
I will make it alright &lt;br /&gt;
because you are beautiful and only the cruelest of worlds, only the most treacherous of people will not love you.&lt;br /&gt;
it does not matter, if we have to close in&lt;br /&gt;
shut off the light&lt;br /&gt;
turn off the life &lt;br /&gt;
it does not matter baby we can run from it me and you&lt;br /&gt;
we can run if they don’t love you&lt;br /&gt;
it’s not your fault &lt;br /&gt;
I will be your last bunker romance if needs be.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 13:46:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/articles/21/my-little-golden-dawn</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/articles/21/my-little-golden-dawn</guid>
        
        
        <category>post</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Will you ever</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Will you ever come back.. to me?
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This waiting room of a life&lt;br /&gt;
I spill out everywhere, and I can’t - yet - drink&lt;br /&gt;
I know I hurt you badly, make you cry&lt;br /&gt;
and even if now I can’t reach you with my voice&lt;br /&gt;
I can reach you with my mind, for here you still exist,&lt;br /&gt;
even tough outside you don’t.&lt;br /&gt;
You are so beautiful, can I just sit?&lt;br /&gt;
Do you know I got so lost?&lt;br /&gt;
It does not really matter, I still carry a picture in my heart.&lt;br /&gt;
Look at me, I am falling down, in the rain&lt;br /&gt;
Look at me, I still smile, you know I like it when you look at me&lt;br /&gt;
Baby, could you make this life even emptier once you are in it?&lt;br /&gt;
Look, I don’t hate on you, for leaving, haha for hating&lt;br /&gt;
don’t mind really&lt;br /&gt;
don’t mind at all,&lt;br /&gt;
why should a man mind of the tallest mountain, when he already walked its highest peak?&lt;br /&gt;
just hug me baby, even if you don’t care&lt;br /&gt;
life is not much better at all, look, it’s all scattered out for you&lt;br /&gt;
I’m leaving you know, leaving you to this beautiful brunch with your friends&lt;br /&gt;
I have a very long walk awaiting, in which I can think of you&lt;br /&gt;
and I will sing:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;“meet me on the other side,&lt;br /&gt;
where as a rose I will wake …”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 13:04:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/articles/21/will-you-ever</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/articles/21/will-you-ever</guid>
        
        
        <category>post</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
